> > 布莱恩: 我想在这里说几件事。
&gt;&gt; Brian: There's a couple things
that I wanna call out here.
重要的是当你编代码的时候
One of the big things is when
you're compiling your code,
设置 NODE_ENV 非常重要。
it's really important that
you set the NODE_ENV..
现在的好消息是
Now, the good news for
如果你是在利用包裹派塞尔就会处理好这个
you is if you're using Parcel,
Parcel just takes care of this.
因此，当您处于开发方式时，它会将其保留在 NODE_ENV=development中。
So when you're in development mode,
it'll keep it in NODE_ENV=development.
然后当你做 Parcel 构建 index.html 时，它会将它设置为生产。
And then when you do a Parcel build
index.html, it'll set that to production.
使用 Web pack 和浏览器文件，您需要更明确一点。
With Web pack and browser file,
you need to be a little more explicit.
>> 布莱恩: 你这样做的原因是当你处于开发模式时
&gt;&gt; Brian: So the reason why you do this
is when you're in development mode,
它会给你更多的描述性错误
it'll give you more descriptive errors.
它会帮你的
It'll kind of help you along the way.
它会阻止你做坏事
It'll prevent you from doing bad things.
然后当你把它放进生产模式时
And then,
when you put it in production mode,
它会像你想要的一样减掉代码
it cuts out as much code as you want or
as it can.
因此，它删除了所有调试代码，使其变得更小更快。
So it drops all of the debugging code,
which makes it smaller and faster.
但是您没有得到有用的错误消息。
But you don't get
the useful error messages.
您不获取源映射。
You don't get source maps.
你不会得到一些帮助你编写代码的东西。
You don't get a bunch of the stuff
that helps you write code.
所以确定这些东西都是在适当的地方
So it's just key to make sure that both of
those things are set in the appropriate
环境。
environments.
> > 布莱恩: 斯拉克，把这个搞砸了，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Slack, famously messed this up,
他们将长期的发展环境运来
that they were shipping the development
environment for a long time.
所以值得关注的是它的大小是它的四倍
So it's worth keeping an eye on
cuz it's four times larger and
如果您使用开发环境，那么会降低 40 倍。
40 times slower if you use
the development environment.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，严格的方式
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, strict mode,
您可以在 React.Strict 中合并整个应用程序。
there's a thing that you can wrap
entire application in React.Strict.
这将会为您提供帮助，帮助您将来的应用证明。
And what this will do for you is it'll
help you future proof your application.
所以， React 有一些事情是他们想去戒除的。
So React has some things that
they're trying to deprecate.
如果你做了 React.Strict ，它就不允许你再使用它们了。
And if you do React.Strict,
it won't allow you to use them anymore.
而如果你没有严格的反应
Whereas if you don't have
React in strict mode,
它会让你用这些东西很快就会被废弃
it'll let you use these things that
they're going to shortly deprecate.
最酷的是它是一个组件，所以你可以在
And the cool thing is it's a component, so
you can make part of your application in
严格方式和部分方式不严格。
strict mode and
part of it not in strict mode.
所以如果你有新的部分申请
So if you have a new
part of your application,
你可以用严格的方式
you can put that in strict mode.
如果你有一个旧的部分会使用 React的旧部分
And if you have an old part that
does use the old part of React,
你仍然可以没有严格的方式
you can still have that
not in strict mode.
让你看看如何做到这一点。
So just to show you how to do that.
事实上，我们可以做得非常快，把它裹起来。
In fact, we can just do it really
quick and leave it in wrap.
转至 wrapper.JS ，然后在此处
Go to wrap.JS, and just here you
可以说 React.StrictMode。
can say React.StrictMode.
我想我的笔记搞错了
I guess I got that wrong in my notes.
所以 React.StrictMode 就像这样
So yeah, React.StrictMode like that.
>> Brian: React.StrictMode 不呈现任何内容，它不添加任何页面权重
&gt;&gt; Brian: React.StrictMode doesn't render
anything, it doesn't add any page weight
或者任何类似的东西，这样做是完全可以的。
or anything like that, so this is
totally fine to ship this to production.
在生产中，这只会无所作为，严格的模式。
In production, this will just do nothing,
the strict mode part of it.
但是现在，如果我们尝试做任何事情，比如使用任何不稳定的 API 或
But now, if we try and do anything
like use any of the unstable APIs or
就像这样
something like that,
它会给你更多关于你不想做的事情的警告
it'll give you additional warnings
about things that you don't want to do.
所以我们是用 JavaScript来教你最新的
So we're teaching you all
the latest in JavaScript.
因此，我们不会触发任何这些警告。
So we won't trigger any of these warnings.
但是如果您在旧应用程序中，那么这可能很有用。
But if you're in legacy applications,
this can be helpful.